export const communityRules = [
    {
        question: '💬 What is this group for?',
        answer: 'This is not the main group of the IT Community of Uzbekistan — it is a space for volunteers to collaborate and communicate. If you’re here, you’re one of us — welcome!',
    },
    {
        question: '🔑 Name, Username & Identity',
        answer: `Use your real full name (Firstname Lastname) in Latin letters, default font.
         Username is required — it helps us communicate and tag each other easily.`,
    },
    {
        question: '📣 Communication Tips',
        answer: 'Please avoid sending just “hi” or “how are you.” Instead, write your full message right away. Why? Read this → aka.ms/nohello',
    },
    {
        question: '🧑‍🤝‍🧑 Keling Tanishaylik Bot',
        answer: 'This bot helps volunteers meet and connect (in-person or online). To participate: \n• Vote “yes” when Shavkat aka sends the poll in the chat. \n• Start the bot (just press Start and keep the chat open).',
    },
    {
        question: '🎉 Can I congratulate someone here?',
        answer: 'We love celebrations! But to avoid message overload, birthdays, holidays, and personal wishes belong in our open-source chat.',
    },
    {
        question: '🚫 Topics to avoid',
        answer: 'Please don’t discuss politics, religion, or personal life details here. Let’s stay focused on collaboration and volunteering.',
    },
    {
        question: '🧺 What is Bazaar Day?',
        answer: 'Every last Sunday of the month, you can promote your:\n• Social media\n• Blogs\n• Side projects\n\n•This is your day to shine — just keep it relevant and respectful!',
    },
    {
        question: '⏰ Discipline = Success',
        answer: 'We value reliability and responsibility. If you’ve committed to something, follow through. Always be on time — ideally, 15 minutes early. That’s the easiest way never to be late 😉',
    },
    {
        question: '📩 This chat is not for outside announcements or promotions',
        answer: 'Please read carefully: IT-related content (posts, links, media): \n•Only allowed if directly related to the IT Community of Uzbekistan or coordinated by @pulsopros (Shavkat aka). \n•Event photos or invitations: Only post if the event was officially co-organized with the community. Not sure? Ask Shavkat first. \n•Job or internship offers: Only allowed if exclusively for our volunteers or approved by Shavkat aka. \n•Personal promotions (e.g. blog, podcast, course): Please wait for Bazaar Day (last Sunday of each month) to share.',
    },
    {
        question: '👥 How can I add my friends to the group?',
        answer: 'Ask your friend to message one of our admins: @pulsopros, @robiya_py, @OmgSoftCode, @camocec, @T_Shamsiddin, @smart_proger_go, @aleeeeeshka, @Fhfnndju, @Gulisa_Ibragimova, @nozima_sharifova, or @MSA1005. They’ll guide them through the selection process',
    },
    {
        question: "🧃Bonus: What's the 2G Community?",
        answer: "Once, Roman (@smart_proger_go) replied to a very old message, and someone joked his internet was on 2G. Since then, “2G Community” became a running gag for those who react late, greet too slowly, or celebrate old news. It's all in good fun 😉",
    },
];
